A Guide to the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission Yucca Mountain Research Collection TD898.12.N3 U85
University of Nevada, Reno. DeLaMare Science & Engineering Library
- Kelderhouse, S. "[LWT, HH and rail transportation graphics. Email communication to J. Shipman, U.S. Department of Energy]." (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Kersting, A.B., Efurd, D.W., Finnegan, D.L. et al. "Migration of plutonium in ground water at the Nevada Test Site." (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Koppenaal, T. "[Responses to Hoganson's questions of 4-2-98. Email communication to M. Hoganson, Office of Civilian Waste Management]." (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Le Camera, R.J. and Locke, G.L. "Selected ground-water data for Yucca Mountain region, Southern Nevada and Eastern California, through December 1996." U.S. Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey. Open-file report 97-821. (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Office of Economics, Section of Energy & Environment. "Draft environmental impact statement finance docket no. 30186 (sub-no. 2) Tongue River Railroad Company - construction and operation of an additional rail line from Aschland to Decker, Montana." (Box 42, Folder 1)
- International Commission on Radiological Protection. "Protection against radon-222 at home and at work." (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Jessen, J. "[Final closure phase years based on March 99 EF's. Email communication to Ikenberry et al., Jason Technologies Corporation]." (Box 42, Folder 3)
- International Commission on Radiological Protection. "1990 recommendations of the International Commission on Radiological Protection." (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Johnson, P.E., Joy, D.S., Clarke, D.B., et al. "Highway 3.1 - An enhanced highway routing model: Program description, methodology, and revised user's manual." D00000000-02268-2003-20012 rev 1 ORNL/TM-12124. Oak Ridge National Laboratory. (Box 42, Folder 5)
- World Health Organization, International Agency for Research on Cancer. "IARC monographs on the evaluation of carcinogenic risks to humans v. 68: Silica, some silicates, coal dust and para-aramid fibrils." (Box 42, Folder 6)
- World Health Organization, International Agency for Research on Cancer. "IARC monographs on the evaluation of carcinogenic risk of chemicals to humans: Silica and some silicates." Vol. 42. (Box 42, Folder 7)
- International Atomic Energy Agency. "Effects of ionizing radiation on plants and animals at levels implied by current radiation protection standards. Technical reports series no. 332." (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Humphreys, S.L., Rollstin, J.A. and Ridgely, J.N. "SECPOP90: Sector population, land fraction, and economic estimation program." Sandia National Laboratories. NUREG/CR-6525 SAND93-4032. (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Geomatrix and TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Saturated zone flow and transport expert elicitation project." (Box 43, Folder 2)
- "Hansen, D.J., Greger, P.D. Wills, C.A. et al. "Nevada Test Site wetlands assessment." Bechtel Nevada Ecological Services. DOE/NV/11718-124. (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Hanson, C.E., Saurenman, H.J. and Towers, D.A. "Rail transportation noise and vibration." From the Handbook of Acoustical Measurements and Noise Control, 3rd ed. (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Harris, M.W. "[Transmittal of biennial hazardous waste report. Letter to W.R. Dixon, Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Office, DOE]." (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Henderson, C.R. Major General, USAF. "[Offer to meet and discuss potential transport of spent fuel to Yucca Mountain. Letter to R. Guida, Naval Nuclear Propulsion Program, Director of Operations and Training, DCS/Air and Space Operations, U.S. Department of the Air Force]." (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Holmes & Narver, Inc. "Feasibility study for transportation facilities to Nevada Test Site." (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Horton, G. "[Respiratory EIS contact report to collect information about water use in Clark County, Lincoln, and Nye Counties. Facsimile to S. LeStrange, Science Applications International Corporation]." (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Hoskins, R.E. "Nuclear waste management systems issues related to transportation cask design: at-reactor spent fuel storage, monitored retrievable storage and modal mix." State of Nevada Agency for Nuclear Projects, Nuclear Waste Project Office. NWPO-TN-003-90. (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Houghton, J.G., Sakamoto, C.M. and Gifford, R.O. "Nevada's weather and climate, special publication no. 2." Nevada Bureau of Mines and Geology and MacKay School of Mines. (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Geomatrix and TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Probabilistic volcanic hazard analysis for Yucca Mountain, Nevada." BA0000000-01717-220-00082 rev.0. Sections 1-5. (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Geomatrix and TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Probabilistic volcanic hazard analysis for Yucca Mountain, Nevada." BA0000000-01717-220-00082 rev.0. Appendices. (Box 44, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of the Interior, U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service. "Recovery plan for the aquatic and riparian species of Pahranagat Valley, Region 1 Portland, Oregon." (Box 44, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of the Interior, U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service. "Railroad Valley springfish recovery plan." (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Fowler, D.D., Madsen, D.B., Hattori, E.M. et al. "Prehistory of southeastern Nevada, Desert Research Institute Publications in the Social Sciences, No. 6." (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Fowler, D.D. and Madsen, D.B. "Prehistory of the southeastern area." From Handbook of North American Indians, vol. 11. (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Fosmire, C. "Location of sloan and Apex IMT with respect to LV Air Basin. Email communication to J. Jessen, Jason Technologies Corporation." TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Flint, A.L., Hevesi, J.A. and Flint, L.E. "Conceptual and numerical model of infiltration for the Yucca Mountain area, Nevada." U.S. Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey. (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Federal Highway Administration and Nevada Department of Transportation. "Northern & Western Las Vegas beltway Clark County, Nevada: Tier 1 final environmental impact statement and corridor location study." FHWA-NV-EIS-95-01-F. (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Federal Emergency Management Agency. "FIRM flood insurance rate map Clark County, Nevada and incorporated areas." Panel 1450 of 4090, map number 32003C1450 D. (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Federal Emergency Management Agency. "FIRM flood insurance rate map Clark County, Nevada and incorporated areas." Map index, map number 32003C0000. (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Federal Bureau of Investigation. "Uniform crime reporting program press release." (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Federal Emergency Management Agency. "FIRM flood insurance rate map Lincoln County, Nevada (unincorporated areas)." Panel 3006 of 5525, community-panel number 320014 3006 C. (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Federal Emergency Management Agency. "FIRM flood insurance rate map Lincoln County, Nevada (unincorporated areas)." Panel 3008 of 5525, community-panel number 320014 3008 C. (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Federal Emergency Management Agency. "FIRM flood insurance rate map Clark County, Nevada and incorporated areas." Panel 3125 of 4090 map number 32003C3125 D. (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Fabryka-Martin, J.T., Wolfsberg, A.V., Levy, S.S. et al. "Evaluation of flow and transport models of Yucca Mountain, based on chlorine-36 and chloride studies for FY98." TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. and Los Alamos National Laboratory. BA0000000-01717-5700-00007, Revision 00. (Box 45, Folder 9)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Uranium, natural, CASRN 7440-61-1." (Box 45, Folder 10)
- ETS Pacific, Inc. "Evaluate alternative rail corridor routes through Lincoln Co., NV to Yucca Mountain, NV." (Box 45, Folder 11)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Toxicological review of hexavalent chromium (CAS No. 18540-29-9) in support of summary information on the integrated risk information system (IRIS)." (Box 45, Folder 12)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Nevada class 1 areas." (Box 45, Folder 13)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "California federal class 1 areas." (Box 45, Folder 14)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Region 9 Nonattainment Areas maps." (Box 45, Folder 15)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Uranium, natural, CASRN 7440-61-1." (Box 45, Folder 16)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Uranium, natural, CASRN 7440-61-1." (Box 45, Folder 17)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, Office of Research and Development. "Ambient levels and noncancer health effects of inhaled crystalline and amorphous silica: Health issue assessment." EPA/600/R-95/115. (Box 46, Folder 1)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, Solid Waste and Emergency Response. "National capacity assessment report: Capacity planning pursuant to CERCLA section 104(c)(9)." EPA530-R-95-016 PB95-209672. (Box 46, Folder 2)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, Office of Water. "Drinking water regulations and health advisories." (Box 46, Folder 3)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, Office of Air Quality Planning and Standards, Emissions, Monitoring, and Analysis Division. "User's guide for the industrial source complex (ISC3) dispersion models." Vol. 1 - user instructions EPA-454/B-95-003a, pp. 1-120. (Box 47, Folder 1)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, Office of Air Quality Planning and Standards, Emissions, Monitoring, and Analysis Division. "User's guide for the industrial source complex (ISC3) dispersion models." Vol. 1 - user instructions EPA-454/B-95-003a, pp. 121-282. (Box 47, Folder 2)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, Office of Radiation and Indoor Air and Oak Ridge National Laboratory. "External exposure to radionuclides in air, water, and soil: Federal guidance report no. 12." EPA 402-R-93-081. (Box 48, Folder 1)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, Office of Radiation Programs and Oak Ridge National Laboratory. "Limiting values of radionuclide intake and air concentration and dose conversion factors for inhalation, submersion, and ingestion: Federal guidance report no. 11." EPA 520/1-88-020. (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Elston, R.B. "Prehistory of the western area." From the Handbook of North American Indians, vol. 11. (Box 48, Folder 3)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Information on levels of environmental noise requisite to protect public health and welfare with an adequate margin of safety." EPA 550/9-74-084. (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Dudley, W.W. Jr. and Larson, J.D. "Effect of irrigation pumping on desert pupfish habitats in Ash Meadows, Nye County, Nevada." Geological survey professional paper 927. U.S. Department of the Interior. (Box 48, Folder 5)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "CAIRS database, DOE and contractor injury and illness experience." (Box 49, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "[Intentionally omitted]." (Box 49, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Record of decision for a multi-purpose canister or comparable system for Idaho National Engineering and Environmental Laboratory spent nuclear fuel." (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Dublyansky, Y.V. "Fluid inclusion studies of samples from the exploratory study facility, Yucca Mountain, Nevada." Institute for Energy and Environmental Research. (Box 49, Folder 4)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Reference design description for a geologic repository." B00000000-01717-5707-00002, Revision 02. (Box 49, Folder 5)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Nevada Operations Office. "Preapproval draft environmental assessment (EA): Intermodal transportation of low level radioactive waste (LLW) to the Nevada Test Site (NTS)." (Box 49, Folder 6)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Environmental Management. "The current and planned low-level waste disposal capacity report." Revision 1. (Box 49, Folder 7)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Viability assessment of a repository at Yucca Mountain." Overview. DOE/RW-0508. (Box 50, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Viability assessment of a repository at Yucca Mountain." DOE/RW-0508. Vol. 1. (Box 50, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Viability assessment of a repository at Yucca Mountain." DOE/RW-0508. Vol. 2. (Box 50, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Viability assessment of a repository at Yucca Mountain." DOE/RW-0508. Vol. 3. (Box 50, Folder 4)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Viability assessment of a repository at Yucca Mountain." DOE/RW-0508. Vol. 4. (Box 50, Folder 5)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Viability assessment of a repository at Yucca Mountain." DOE/RW-0508. Vol. 5. (Box 50, Folder 6)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Nevada routes for legal-weight truck shipments of SNF and HLW to Yucca Mountain [map]." YMP-97-3103. (Box 50, Folder 7)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Potential rail corridors [map]." YMP-98-179.0. (Box 50, Folder 8)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Potential rail alignments [map]." YMP-98-104.0. (Box 50, Folder 9)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Nevada routes for heavy-haul truck shipments of SNF and HLW to Yucca Mountain [map]." YMP-97-263.9. (Box 50, Folder 10)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Disturbances at Yucca Mountain since June 21, 1991 [map]." (Box 50, Folder 11)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Existing pre-repository site conditions." (Box 50, Folder 12)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Intermodal transfer site - Caliente siting area map." BCBI00000-01717-2700-82038, revision 00. (Box 50, Folder 13)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Total system performance assessment - 1995: An evaluation of the potential Yucca Mountain repository." B00000000-01717-2200-00136, revision 01. Ch. 1. (Box 51, Folder 1)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Total system performance assessment - 1995: An evaluation of the potential Yucca Mountain repository." B00000000-01717-2200-00136, revision 01. Ch. 2-4. (Box 51, Folder 2)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Total system performance assessment - 1995: An evaluation of the potential Yucca Mountain repository." B00000000-01717-2200-00136, revision 01. Ch. 5-6. (Box 51, Folder 3)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Total system performance assessment - 1995: An evaluation of the potential Yucca Mountain repository." B00000000-01717-2200-00136, revision 01. Ch. 7-8. (Box 51, Folder 4)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Total system performance assessment - 1995: An evaluation of the potential Yucca Mountain repository." B00000000-01717-2200-00136, revision 01. Ch. 9-11. (Box 51, Folder 5)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Nevada potential repository preliminary transportation strategy study 1." B00000000-01717-4600-00023, revision 01. (Box 52, Folder 1)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Repository subsurface layout options and ESF interface." B00000000-01717-5705-00009, revision 00. (Box 52, Folder 2)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Health and safety impacts analysis for the multi-purpose canister system and alternatives." A00000000-01717-0200-00006, revision 2. (Box 52, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management, Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project. "Socioeconomic monitoring program 1994 U.S. Department of Energy/Nevada employee survey data report executive summary." (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Toblin, A.L. "Final radionuclide transport and dose commitment from drinking water from continued storage and degradation of spent nuclear fuel and high-level waste materials under loss of institutional control." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Timbisha Shoshone Tribe and the Department of the Interior. "The Timbisha Shoshone Tribal homeland: A draft secretarial report to congress to establish a permanent tribal land base and related cooperative activities." (Box 52, Folder 6)
- "[EIS questions on electrical system. Email communications between Thurman, K., Beyer, J., Bauhaus, M. and LeSrange, S]." Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System and Science Applications International Corporation. (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Thomas, J.M., Welch, A.H. and Dettinger, M.D. "Geochemistry and isotope hydrology of representative aquifers in the Great Basin region of Nevada, Utah, and adjacent states: Regional aquifer-system analysis." U.S. Geological Survey professional paper 1409-C. (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Thomas, D.H., Pendleton, L.S.A. and Cappannari, S.C. "Western Shoshone." From the Handbook of North American Indians, vol. 11. (Box 52, Folder 9)
- U.S. Department of the Interior. "Methods for estimating magnitude and frequency of floods in the Southwestern United States: United States Geological Survey water-supply." Paper 2433. (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Thiel Engineering Consultants. "Data assessment water rights/resource analysis of: Hydrographic region #14 Death Valley basin." (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Tappen, J.J. and W.B. Andrews. "Preliminary rail access study." U.S Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Waste Management, Yucca Mountain Project. DOE/YMP-89-16. (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Szymanski, J.S. "Conceptual considerations of the Yucca Mountain groundwater system with special emphasis on the adequacy of this system to accommodate a high-level nuclear waste repository." U.S. Department of Energy, Nevada Operations Office, Yucca Mountain Project Office. Vol. 1. (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Szymanski, J.S. "Conceptual considerations of the Yucca Mountain groundwater system with special emphasis on the adequacy of this system to accommodate a high-level nuclear waste repository." U.S. Department of Energy, Nevada Operations Office, Yucca Mountain Project Office. Vol. 2. (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Szymanski, J.S. "Conceptual considerations of the Yucca Mountain groundwater system with special emphasis on the adequacy of this system to accommodate a high-level nuclear waste repository." U.S. Department of Energy, Nevada Operations Office, Yucca Mountain Project Office. Vol. 3. (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Strifflier, P., O'Brien, G.M., Oliver, T. et al. "Draft perched water characteristics and occurrences, Yucca Mountain, Nevada." U.S. Geological Survey. (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Sygitowicz, L.S., Bechdel, Nevada. "[Annual Nevada Test Site solid waste disposal reports - 1997. Letter to K.A. Hoar, Nevada Operations Office, DOE]." (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Stoffle, R.W., Evans, M.J. and Harshbarger, C.L. "Native American interpretation of cultural resources in the area of Yucca Mountain, Nevada interim report." Institute for Social Research, University of Michigan. DOE/NV-10576-17 SAIC-88/8011. (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Stoffle, R.W., Olmstead, J.E. and Evans, M.J. "Literature review and ethnohistory of Native American occupancy and use of the Yucca Mountain region interim report." Institute for Social Research, University of Michigan. DOE/NV-10576-21. (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Stoffle, R.W. "Native Americans and nuclear waste storage at Yucca Mountain, Nevada: Potential impacts of site characterization activities." Institute for Social Research, University of Michigan. (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Stoffle, R.W., Evans, M.J., Halmo, D.B. et al. "Native American plant resources in the Yucca Mountain area, Nevada interim report." Institute for Social Research, University of Michigan. DOE/NV-10576-19. (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Squires, R.R. and Young, R.L. "Flood potential of Fortymile Wash and its principal southwestern tributaries, Nevada Test Site, Southern Nevada." U.S. Geological Survey water-resources investigations report 83-4001. (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Spotila, J.R., Zimmerman, L.C., Binckley, C.A. et al. "Effects of incubation conditions on sex determination, hatching success, and growth of hatchling desert tortoises, Gopherus agassizii." From Herpetological Monographs. (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Souleyrette, R.R. II, Sathisan, S.K. and di Bartolo, R. "Yucca Mountain transportation routes: Preliminary characterization and risk analysis." State of Nevada Agency for Nuclear Waste Projects/Nuclear Waste Project Office, Transportation Research Center. NWPO-TN-011-91. Vol. I: Research report. (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Southern Nevada Water Authority. "Water resources frequently asked questions." (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Southern Nevada Water Authority. "Water wise [newsletter]." (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Smith, R.I., Daling, P.M. and Faletti, D.W. ""Analysis of radiation doses from operation of postulated commercial spent fuel transportation systems: Analysis of a system containing a monitored retrievable storage facility." Pacific Northwest Laboratory and the U.S. Department of Energy, Chicago Field Office. DOE-CH/TPO-001 Addendum 1. (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Simonds, F.W., Whitney, J.W., Fox, K.F. et al. "Map showing fault activity in the Yucca Mountain area, Nye County, Nevada." U.S. Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey. MAP I-2520. (Box 54, Folder 11)
- "[Telephone conversation between M. Bauhaus and M. Sherwood, re: numbers on concrete not cement.]" (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Scott, R.B. and Bonk, J. "Preliminary geological map of Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada, with geologic sections." U.S. Geological Survey, U.S. Department of the Interior. OFR-84-494. (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Schneider, K.J., Ross, W.A., Smith, R.I. et al. "Analysis of radiation doses from operation of postulated commercial spent fuel transportation systems." Pacific Northwest Laboratory. DOE-CH/TPO-001. (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Sawyer, D.A., Fleck, R.J, Lanphere, M.A. et al. "Episodic caldera volcanism in the Miocene Southwestern Nevada volcanic field." From Geological Society of America Bulletin. (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Savage, J.C., Lisowski, M., Gross, W.K. et al. "Strain accumulation near Yucca Mountain, Nevada 1983-1993." From Journal of Geophysical Research. (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Saricks, C.L. and Tompkins, M.M. "State-level accident rates of surface freight transportation: A reexamination." Argonne National Laboratory Transportation Technology R&D Center. (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Rush, F. E. "Water resources-reconnaissance series report 54: Regional ground-water systems in the Nevada Test Site area, Nye, Lincoln, and Clark Counties, Nevada." U.S. Geological Survey, U.S. Department of the Interior. (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Ross, S. "[Cask fleet size for mostly LWT scenario. Email communication to K. House, Battelle Memorial Institute.]" (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Rodefer, T.R. (ed.), Selmi, S., Butler, J. et al. "Nevada statistical abstract 1996." The Nevada Department of Administration. (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Resource Concepts, Inc. "Soil survey of Yucca Mountain study area, Nye County, Nevada." (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Regional Economic Models, Inc. "Product information and pricing." (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Raytheon Services Nevada. "Draft white paper subject: High speed surface transportation between Las Vegas and the Nevada Test Site." (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Rautenstrauch, K.R., Brown, G.A. and Goodwin, R.G. "Northern boundary of the desert tortoise range on the Nevada Test Site." EG and G Energy Measurements, Inc. (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Rautenstrauch, K.R. and O'Farrell, T.P. "Relative abundance of desert tortoises on the Nevada Test Site." From Southwestern Naturalist. (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Poe, W.L. Jr. "Long term environmental analysis of total inventory of spent nuclear fuel and high-level waste for no-action alternative of Yucca Mountain environmental impact statement." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. Revision 1. (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Poe, W.L. Jr. "Final regional binning for continued storage of spent nuclear fuel and high-level wastes." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. Revision 1. (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Portland General Electric. "Trojan ISFSI safety analysis report." TOC - ch. 4 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Portland General Electric. "Trojan ISFSI safety analysis report." Ch. 5-11 (Box 55, Folder 16)